Do you know about personality rehabilitation?
인격 교정에 관한 얘기 들어봤어?
There is a secret I don't know.
이 나라에 내가 모르는 비밀이 있어
Beware of this country.
조심해... 이 나라는...
They want you...
너를...
What was the secret?
그 비밀의 정체를
My father knew.
아빠는 알고 있었어
My brother too.
형도...
I want to know the answer.
나도... 그 비밀이 궁금해
This incident is a declaration of war by Seiran
이번 사건은 카렌과 세이란시가
to the New Himuka Government.
뉴히무카 정부에 선전포고한 거다
Is that why they retreated?
그래서... 철수한 겁니까?
So the assassination of Chairman Sumeragi...
그럼 스메라기 의장님을 암살한 것도...
Yes, it was orchestrated by Karen and the Seiran Force.
그래, 카렌과 세이란시의 명령이다
From what I heard, half of our members have defected to Seiran.
절반 이상의 대원들이 세이란에 합류했다고 들었습니다
Yes.
그렇다
We will restructure the remaining forces of OSF.
남은 토벌군은 새롭게 팀을 이룰 것이다
From now on, you will carry out your mission as Platoon 01.
앞으로 너희는 01소대의 신분으로 임무를 수행한다
Yuito will be your captain.
대장은... 유이토다
You want me as their captain?
제가요?
As I mentioned earlier, I need you to be a hero.
난 네가 영웅이 되길 원한다
Become the hero who defends this country.
뉴히무카를 지키는 영웅 말이다
SCARLET NEXUS
"스칼렛넥서"
♫A crime in reality♫
현실의 Crimｅ
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven`s sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
거짓을 받아들여
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
영원한 환상은 점점 사라져가
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
결코 완벽하지 않아 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
뒤돌아 걸어오는 소녀는
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
순간 이 세상에 기적을 남겨
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
최고의 게임을 찾았어
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I`ve never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
난 언제부터 이런 세상이 질렸던 걸까
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won`t be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
더는 해치고 싶지 않기에 나를 희생해
Yuito.
유이토
What's wrong? You just stopped moving.
갑자기 멈춰서서 뭐해?
"PURSUING NAGI" Yuito.
(추적, 나기) 유이토
I thought we were at the headquarters.
우리... 본부에 있는 거 아니었어?
What are you talking about?
그게 무슨 말이야?
Sorry for the long wait.
오래 기다렸지
I rejected all requests for an interview
까마귀들을 접근 못 하게 하려고
to keep Crows away.
인터뷰하러 오지 못하도록 막았어
Lieutenant Colonel Luka.
루카 중좌...
You may address me as Luka.
그냥 루카라고 불러도 돼
Yuito, you are the captain now.
넌 대장이잖아
Wait, why am I the captain?
잠깐만, 내가 대장이라고?
What's going on?
이게 다 어떻게 된 거지?
Yuito...
유이토
Yuito is weird.
유이토가 이상해
Wataru, is there any anomaly with Yuito's brain activities?
와타루, 유이토 대뇌 데이터에 에러라도 난 거야?
No, everything is normal.
아니, 전혀
We've been reassigned as Platoon 01 of OSF.
소대 재편성으로 우리는 01소대
You are our new captain.
그리고 넌 대장으로 임명됐어
We are on patrol at the moment.
지금은 순찰 임무 수행 중이야
I remember now. We were meeting my brother.
그래, 형이 나를 불렀어
And then...
그 뒤로...
I can't remember what happened next.
아무것도 기억이 안 나
Did I ask him about the country's secret?
이 나라의 비밀에 대해 형한테 확인했었나...
Do you really not remember anything?
진짜 기억이 안 나?
Yes.
응...
I have a bad feeling about this.
느낌이 안 좋아
We should send him to the OSF hospital.
빨리 토벌군병원에 가보는 게 좋겠어
If you're not feeling well, I can inform the superior for you.
진짜 몸이 불편하면 내가 위에 얘기해둘게
My uncle is the hospital's Chief Director. I'll contact him for you.
우리 큰아빠가 토벌군병원 이사장이셔, 내가 연락해볼게
If I message him,
메시지만 보내두면
he can have you checked in no time.
바로 안배할 수 있어서 금방 진찰할 수 있을 거야
We will stay to carry out the mission.
우리는 여기서 임무 수행하자
Yuito, you're the captain. We can ask you to risk your health.
내가 대장을 강박하진 못하지만...
It's best to have a doctor look at you.
그래도 진찰하는게 좋을 것 같아
Okay, Yuito?
어때, 유이토?
Now,
지금부터
I will announce the result of Seiran OSF structure.
세이란 토벌군 소대 편성 결과를 발표한다
Platoon 01.
01소대
Kyoka Eden.
쿄카 에덴
Arashi Spring.
아라시 스프링
Kagero Donne.
카게로 던
Shiden Ritter.
시덴 리터
Haruka Frazer.
하루카 프레이저
Captain Kasane Randall.
대장, 카사네 랜들
New Himuka wasn't satisfied with social management,
뉴히무카는 사회관리 시스템 구축뿐만 아니라
so they started the forbidden experiments.
금기된 연구도 시작했다
Experiments to turn humans into Others.
인류를 괴이로 변화시키는 연구 말이야?
They were researching a way to create outstanding power users.
그들은 우수한 초뇌능력자를 만드는 방법
During the process,
연구 과정에
they developed the experiment to turn creatures into Others.
생물의 괴이화 실험을 강행했다
I want to overthrow the New Himuka government that conducted those horrible experiments.
난 괴이화 실험을 하는 뉴히무카 정부를 쓰러뜨릴 것이다
You should come to Seiran.
너희도 세이란시에 합류하기 바란다
Was it New Himuka that turn Naomi into a monster?
나오미를 괴이로 변하게 한 것도 뉴히무카 정부야?
Yes.
그렇다
Naomi is in Seiran.
나오미를 세이란시에서
Can you save her?
구할 수 있어?
I will do my best.
최선을 다해보겠다
Understood.
알았어
I shall go to Seiran as well.
그럼 나도 세이란시에 갈게
I didn't expect to see all of you in Seiran.
어쩌다 보니 다들 세이란에 와있네
Seiran was my hometown anyway.
난 본가가 세이란시에 있어
And I despise New Himuka's conduct.
게다가 뉴히무카 정부의 행위도 마음에 안 들고
I'm just killing time.
여기에서 시간 보내는 거지 뭐
Lady Kyoka is here too.
쿄카님도 와있네
Are you a fan of Karen's?
설마 카렌의 팬인가?
Is it so surprising that I'm his fan?
내가 카렌 연대장님의 팬인게 이상해?
For real?
진짜라고?
I'm just kidding.
농담이야
As a commander,
지휘관의 입장에서
I'm against the government's suspicious actions.
정부가 이상한 행동을 하는 건 나도 싫어
Not to mention they conducted experiments to turn humans into Others.
게다가 인류를 괴이로 변하게 하는 연구를 했다니
That's unforgivable.
용서가 안 돼
It seems like the people of Seiran don't trust the New Himuka government at all.
세이란시에 온 사람은 모두 정부를 믿지 못하는 거네
But Major General Karen's reputation got him a lot of followers.
카렌 연대장님의 명성 덕분에 많은 사람을 끌어들이긴 했지만
Where is Kasane?
참, 카사네는?
Who knows?
나도 몰라
No one has seen her after the gathering.
집회가 끝나고는 사라졌어
My sister is somewhere in this city.
언니가 이 도시 어딘가에 있어
CONNECTION FAILED
(통화 불가)
The hero who assassinated Chairman Sumeragi is on our side.
스메라기 평의회 의장을 암살한 영웅이 우리에게 합류해서
The higher-ups of Seiran are glad to hear that.
세이란의 고관들이 아주 기뻐해
I didn't kill him.
내가 죽인게 아니야
Does it matter if you get to be the hero?
영웅이 되는 것도 나쁘지 않지
Make use of that title.
그 명의를 이용하면 되는 거잖아
Seiran is using me for their bidding.
세이란에서 나를 이용하는 거겠지
It doesn't matter. Where is Naomi now?
그것보다 나오미가 어디에 있는지 알려줘
It has been confirmed that above the Kunad Highway
쿠나도 고속도로 상공에
is a partial singularity.
부분적 중력 이상 현상이 확인됐어
It's expanding.
점점 커지고 있군
Yes.
예
It's consuming everything around it and growing.
주변 사물들을 삼키면서 점차 커지고 있습니다
The New Himuka Government called it the Kunad Gate.
뉴히무카 정부는 저것을 쿠나도 게이트라고 하지
The thing slowly grew without us even noticing it.
저건 어느샌가 점점 더 커졌지
You and I created this.
저건 너랑 내가 만들었던
It's like a black hole.
블랙홀 같은...
It's called the Kunad Gate.
쿠나도 게이트야
As you can see, the hold is still consuming our world.
점차 커지면서 세상을 삼키는 저 블랙홀을 너도 봤을 거야
Just as I expected.
역시 맞았네
Kasane, you've been to the future.
카사네, 너 미래에 다녀왔지?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이야?
Let's not waste my time.
내 시간을 낭비하지 말고
Tell me,
어서 대답해
what did you see in the future?
미래에서 뭘 본 건지
He can tell I've been to the future.
내가 미래에 다녀온 걸 알고 있어
It's futile to keep it a secret now.
숨기고 싶지만 어쩔 수 없지
At the end of the world,
곧 멸망하는 세계에서
I ran into you.
너를 만났어
What did my future self tell you?
미래의 내가 뭐라고 했지?
There's hope after all.
이제 됐어
Is that so?
그래?
Did you mean there was a chance to save those who were turned into Others?
네 말은 괴이화된 인류를 구할 방법이 있다는 거야?
Karen, what more do you know?
카렌, 넌 대체 뭘 알고 있는 거지?
If you have a way to turn Others back to human beings,
괴이로 변한 인류가 원상복구 되는 방법을 알고 있다면
then Naomi can be saved.
나오미도 구할 수 있다는 거겠지?
All I can tell you for now
내가 알려줄 수 있는 정보는
is that researchers in Seiran
세이란의 연구기관에서
are conducting researches related to Others.
괴이와 관련된 연구를 진행하고 있다는 것뿐이야
That's where they keep Naomi.
나오미가 거기에 있는 거지?
Yes, she is safe there.
그래, 그곳에서 보호 중이야
Where are they conducting the research?
연구기관이 어디에 있는지 말해
I cannot tell you.
말할 수 없어
The research is highly confidential.
그곳에서 극비 연구 진행 중이라
Outsiders are not allowed into the facility.
일반인은 접근할 수 없어
I am no outsider.
난 일반인이 아닌데
Tell me, or I'll resort to violence.
말해주지 않는다면 힘을 쓸 수밖에
So here you are!
너 여기에 있었구나
Arashi.
아라시
I'm sorry to interrupt the conversation.
대화 중에 끼어들어 미안한데
It's time for our mission.
임무 수행하러 갈 시간이야
We can set out for our mission without the captain.
대장이 없으면 임무를 수행할 수 없어서 말이지
Arashi, keep an eye on this reckless brat.
아라시, 여기 사나운 친구를 부탁해
Arashi, why did you stop me?
아라시, 왜 막았어?
You are always so reckless when Naomi is involved.
나오미와 연관된 일이라면 넌 막 나가잖아
I overheard everything. You want to get into the facility.
다 들었거든, 연구기관에 가고 싶다며?
You have all the more reason not to get into trouble.
그렇다면 더더욱 사고 치면 안 되잖아
I don't understand.
그게 무슨 말이야?
Before you start opposing your superior, you must act like an obedient soldier.
상급에게 반항하려면 일단 착한척해야지 않겠어?
Are you willing to help me get to Naomi?
나오미를 찾는 걸 도와주겠다는 거야?
Certainly.
물론이지
After all, she is one of us.
우리는 파트너이니까
I'll gather information about the facility.
내가 연구기관 정보를 얻는 걸 도와줄게
For the time being, behave and carry out your mission.
그러니까 일단 임무나 착실히 수행하자고
"YUITO" That's about it.
(유이토) 대략 이런 상황이야
In any case, there is no need to worry.
그러니까 너무 걱정 말고
We will prescribe some medicine for you.
병원에서 약을 줄 테니
Take the pills when the symptoms show up.
증상이 나타날 때마다 먹으면 돼
Okay.
네
Thank you, doctor.
감사합니다, 선생님
Yuito, how was it?
유이토, 뭐래?
It was caused by extreme fatigue.
피로가 쌓여서
Over-secretion of psionic hormone
초감각의 자극으로 호르몬 분비가 넘쳐나
caused the part of the brain that controls memories
뇌의 기억을 관리하는 부분에
become confused.
혼란이 생겼다고...
That's all.
그래서 그런 거래
Some medication will get me back on my feet.
약 먹으면 괜찮을 거래
I see.
그렇구나
I'm glad to hear that.
다행이다
By the way...
그나저나...
MUSCLE DANCE
(근육 운동)
Thankfully it wasn't any serious condition.
큰 문제가 아니라서 다행이야, 유이토
I don't understand what the girls like nowadays.
요즘 여자들의 취미는 이해가 안 되는군
Too much had happened since you joined the force.
입대후 많은 일이 있었으니
It's normal if you feel exhausted.
피로를 느끼는 것도 정상이야
You're low on spirit.
기운이 없어
You need more water.
수분이 부족해
Why is everyone here?
왜 다들 여기에 와있는 거야?
Don't worry.
걱정 마
We carried out our mission and completed the patrol.
순찰 임무는 이미 끝냈어
Tsugumi was worried about you.
그리고 츠구미가 엄청 걱정했어
Does Yuito need a lot of water too?
유이토도 수분 필요해?
You just got promoted, don't give yourself too much stress.
이제 막 대장이 되었으니까 너무 애쓰지 마
If there is anything we can help you with,
내가 뭐 도와줄 건 없어?
feel free to tell us.
마음껏 얘기해
Thank you, everyone.
다들 고마워
During the turmoils in Suoh, he bravely fought against the Others.
스오 사건에서 과감히 괴이를 토벌하고
"A HERO IS BORN" He's the hero of Suoh,
(영웅의 탄생) 스오를 구한 영웅
Private Yuito Sumeragi.
유이토 스메라기 상병
"2ND LIEUTENANT YUITO SUMERAGI, 16" Because of his gallant feat, he's been promoted
(유이토 스메라기 소위, 16세) 이번의 뛰어난 표현으로 소위에 진급했고
"THE NATIONAL HERO APPOINTED AS CAPTAIN" and appointed the captain of Platoon 01.
(구국 영웅, 새로운 대장으로 임명) 01소대의 새로운 대장으로 임명되었습니다
What? When did they interview me?
뭐야, 내가 언제 인터뷰를 했어?
I have no recollection of this at all.
난 왜 기억이 안 나지?
Up next, we have footage of our national hero's heroic combat on the battlefield.
이어서 구국 영웅 유이토 스메라기 소위의 전투 중 모습을 보여드립니다
Yuito, I know it leaves a bad taste in you.
유이토, 네가 원하지 않는다는 거 알아
But please bear with it.
하지만 참아줬으면 좋겠어
You must become our national hero.
넌 반드시 구국 영웅이 되어야만 해
We lost the council and the Chairman.
평의회 의장님의 사망으로
Our people are in a panic.
국민이 혼란을 겪고 있어
You must become their beacon of hope.
그러니 네가 반드시 모두의 희망이 되어야 해
But I still remember the conversation.
그 대화들이 생각났어
Was there anything else?
그리고 또 뭐가 있었지?
No, I can't recall any memory.
안돼, 역시 생각이 안 나
The traitor Kasane Randall brutally assassinated Chairman Sumeragi.
국적 카사네 랜들이 조 스메라기 평의회 의장님을 해쳤고
2nd Lieutenant Yuito Sumeragi overcame the sadness of this tragedy
유이토 스메라기 소위는 이 갑작스러운 악몽에서 벗어나
and stood out to fight for New Himuka's future.
뉴히무카를 위해 과감히 대항했습니다
We don't get to come here every day. Why not take a tour around here?
어쩌다 병원까지 왔는데 구경이나 해볼래?
Let me show you around.
내가 구경시켜줄게
That's a nice idea.
그것도 좋겠네
Rather than watching hyped-up news by the Crows,
까마귀들이 흥분해서 날뛰는 뉴스보다
a tour doesn't sound that bad.
병원을 구경하는게 낫겠어
I agree.
나도 찬성이야
It takes some time to get the medicine ready.
처방약을 기다리려면 시간이 필요하잖아
Okay, let's do it.
그래, 그렇게 하자
Sorry.
잠깐만
Excuse me, how may I help you?
혹시 도움이 필요하세요?
How do I get to the Neurology Department?
뇌신경과에 가려면 어떻게 가야 하죠?
Let's see...
잠시만요
Follow the signs over there.
저기 표지판을 따라가시면 돼요
NEUROLOGY
(뇌신경과)
Sorry, I can't see it...
죄송한데 안 보이네요...
That's because I'm a Bell Pepper...
제가 벨 페퍼라서...
I can't see signs that use the psionic system to operate.
뇌능력 시스템으로 된 표지판을 볼 수가 없어요...
I can take you there.
그럼 제가 안내해드릴게요
Sorry, it won't take long.
미안, 나 금방 다녀올게
All right.
그래
-Follow me. -I'm sorry for the trouble.
-이쪽으로 오세요 -죄송합니다
The Vision Town and psynet,
거리 영상과 사이넷
and even Arahabaki
아라하바키 시스템은
were created based on the presumption that everyone has access to brain powers.
뇌능력의 전제하에서 만들어진 거야
From what I heard, around 0.1% of the population are Bell Peppers.
1퍼센트의 사람들이 벨 페퍼라고 하던데
The government should care more about the minority.
정부에서 이런 사람들도 고려해주면 좋을 텐데
"NEUROLOGY" Here we are.
(뇌신경과) 여기예요
Thank you.
감사합니다
Don't mention it.
뭘요
See you.
그럼
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
(관계자 외 출입 금지)
Nagi...
나기...
You saw Nagi?
나기?
They took him to an elevator that leads to the underground.
엘리베이터 타고 지하층으로 내려갔어
Could I have mistaken someone for him?
내가 잘못 봤나?
Sorry, I can't get any access.
미안, 추적이 안 돼
I can't get into the hospital's system.
내가 병원 시스템은 들어가지 못해서 말이야
I found it.
찾았다
Nagi is in the underground tunnel.
나기가 지하도로에 있어
He's been brought onto a car. I don't know where they are headed.
사람들이 차에 옮겼는데 어디로 가는지 몰라
Underground tunnels lead to the city area.
지하도로라면 시내 지역으로 향하는 거네
Do you know which direction they went?
어느 방향인지 보여?
Hold on.
잠깐만
I think they are headed to Lokusho City.
로쿠쇼시 방향인 것 같아
Lokusho City?
로쿠쇼시?
The city that was destroyed instantly after the Other attacked 11 years ago.
11년 전 괴이의 공격으로 파멸된 도시 말인가?
Yuito, you and your mother...
유이토, 너랑 네 어머니가...
There is an old facility of the OSF hospital in Lokusho City.
로쿠쇼시에는 토벌군병원의 "구관"이 있어
Yes.
맞아
But if I remember correctly, that place has been abandoned.
거긴 이미 폐관한 것으로 알고 있는데
I think so too.
나도 그렇게 알고 있어
If Nagi is really there,
진짜 나기가 맞다면
if he's still alive,
아직 살아있는 거라면
I must talk to him.
나기와 얘기해보고 싶어
I hope everyone could come with me.
다들 같이 가줬으면 좋겠어
That's the abandoned OSF hospital facility.
저기가 바로 토벌군병원의 구관이야
There is nothing around it.
주위에 아무것도 없어
I thought the Others are only interested in human brains.
괴이의 목표는 사람의 뇌라고 하지 않았어?
How did it become so desolate?
어쩌다 이런 황무지로 변한 거지?
I found the car.
자동차를 찾았어
But Nagi is not in it.
하지만 그 안에 나기는 없어
Is he inside the building?
건물 안에는?
There are places I can't see through.
많은 곳이 투시가 안 돼
So this place is still operating.
역시 여전히 운영하고 있네
What does that mean?
무슨 뜻이야?
I've heard rumors.
그런 소문을 들었었어
Some kind of institute seemed to conduct experiments in this building.
어떤 기관이 구관에서 뭔가를 연구하고 있다고
The surrounding buildings might have been removed
주변 건축물을 없애버린 건
by the New Himuka Government.
아마도 뉴히무카 정부인 것 같아
Wataru, can you check what's inside the building?
와타루, 구관 내부가 보여?
I can't access the data about this old facility.
구관에 관련된 자료는 불러오지 못해
I advise you to be cautious.
내가 돕지 못하는 범위니까 조심해
Understood.
알았어
All right.
좋아
We'll proceed with cautions.
다들 신중히 움직여
This is incredible.
너무 놀라워
It's consuming everything around it.
주위 사물을 계속 삼키고 있어
What happens to the things that go in there?
안으로 들어가면 어떨지 궁금하네
That's right, Shiden. Try putting your hand in it.
참, 시덴, 저기에 손 집어넣어 봐
Why don't you stick your head into it?
네 머리부터 집어넣지 그래
Cut it out.
그만해
Stop fooling around, and don't get too close.
농담도 하지 말고 가까이 가지도 마
Curiosity kills the cat.
호기심 많은 고양이는 다칠 수 있으니까
I remember this feeling.
이 느낌을 기억해
I felt it when the Red Strings were triggered.
붉은 실과... 레드 스트링스가 작동될 때의 느낌과 비슷해
That means...
그렇다는 건...
Our powers
너와 내 초뇌능력은
share the same property of manipulating gravity.
같은 유형의 중력 조작이야
Our powers resonated
우리의 힘이 공감을 생성해
and gave birth to the Kunad Gate.
쿠나도 게이트를 만든 거야
The future Yuito was right after all.
50년 뒤의 유이토 스메라기 말이 맞았어
What's on your mind?
무슨 생각 해?
Are you thinking about the Kunad Gate you saw in the future?
미래에서 본 쿠나도 게이트 모습이 생각난 거야?
That's when you met the future Yuito.
미래의 유이토 스메라기를 만났을 때 말이야
He was like a different person.
완전 다른 사람 같았어
He didn't care if he lost his life.
아랑곳하지 않고 자신을 희생하는
I feel sad for him.
가여운 사람
Do you plan to take his life before he turns into that sorry state?
그래서 유이토가 그렇게 변하기 전에 죽이고 싶은 거야?
So he won't feel any pain?
유이토가 고통스러워하지 않도록?
My mother was here.
그때 엄마가 여기에 있었어...
You must live on.
넌 꼭 살아남아야 해
That person and I...
나와 그 사람...
What's wrong?
뭐야?
We have intruders. What's going on?
누군가 들어왔어, 어떻게 된 거야?
Is something wrong, Yuito?
왜 그래, 유이토?
Does this place remind you of the time you spent in the hospital?
입원했을 때 일이 생각난 거야?
That's impossible. I was too young back then.
아니, 너무 어렸을 때라 그런가?
I couldn't remember what happened.
그때의 일들이 별로 기억이 안 나
Above us!
위에 조심해
Yuito!
유이토
Excuse me!
미안
Sorry, I can only see through the horizontal areas.
미안해, 난 수평 방향만 투시할 수 있어
Thanks, Hanabi.
고마워, 하나비
Don't mention it. Stay alert.
아니야, 조심해
Here it comes.
오고 있어
The reaction became stronger.
반응이 갑자기 격렬해졌어
The singularity is expanding.
중력 이상 상황이 커지고 있어요
How did this happen?
갑자기 왜 이러는 거지?
We have no idea.
글쎄요
Kunad Gate, growth rate increased by 5%.
쿠나도 게이트가 성장률이 5퍼센트 상승했습니다
Nagi!
나기
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
운명의 지시 따윈 필요 없어
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
분명 고쳐질 거라 믿으니까
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
앞으로도 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 말이야
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
눈부시게 빛나는 태양이 막을 내리고
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
세상의 끝에서 뭘 기다리고 있는걸까
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
♫Who can shake us♫
누가 우리를 위협해
♫Who can define us♫
누가 우리 대신 결정해
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
이건 우리만의 스토리야
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
네 마음속 미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
TRUTH HIDDEN IN THE HOSPITAL
(병원의 진실)